import { QuestionType } from "../../types";

export const multipleChoiceQuestion: QuestionType[] = [
  {
    questionId: "1",
    questionText: "Which one is the correct statement?",
    descriptionText: "",
    options: [
      {
        id: "A",
        text: "A descriptive text is a text that tells a story, an action, or an activities of someone or an animal.",
      },
      {
        id: "B",
        text: "A descriptive text is a text that gives entertainment to the reader.",
      },
      {
        id: "C",
        text: "A text that says what a person or a thing is like is called a descriptive text.",
      },
      {
        id: "D",
        text: "A descriptive text is text which gives imaginative story about a person, a thing, or an animal.",
      },
      {
        id: "E",
        text: "A descriptive text is a text that tells about experiences or phenomenon.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "B",
  },
  {
    questionId: "2",
    questionText: "What is the definition of descriptive text?",
    descriptionText: "",
    options: [
      {
        id: "A",
        text: "It is a text that explains how to do something.",
      },
      {
        id: "B",
        text: "It is a text that presents information about something in general based on research.",
      },
      {
        id: "C",
        text: "It is a text that describes a particular object in detail.",
      },
      {
        id: "D",
        text: "It is a text that describes a sequence of events.",
      },
      {
        id: "E",
        text: "It is a text that explains a process, event, or action in a clear, logical, and simple way.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "C",
  },
  {
    questionId: "3",
    questionText: "What is the generic structure of descriptive text?",
    descriptionText: "",
    options: [
      {
        id: "A",
        text: "Introduction, Conclusion",
      },
      {
        id: "B",
        text: "General Classification, Description",
      },
      {
        id: "C",
        text: "Orientation, Complication, Resolution",
      },
      {
        id: "D",
        text: "Title, Explanation, Conclusion",
      },
      {
        id: "E",
        text: "Identification, Description",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "E",
  },
  {
    questionId: "4",
    questionText:
      "The use of linguistic elements in descriptive text aims to make the text can be read and understood easily. As for the language features in descriptive text, except...",
    descriptionText: "",
    options: [
      {
        id: "A",
        text: "Using simple past tense",
      },
      {
        id: "B",
        text: "Using adjective",
      },
      {
        id: "C",
        text: "Using action verb",
      },
      {
        id: "D",
        text: "Using figurative language",
      },
      {
        id: "E",
        text: "Using adverb",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A",
  },
  {
    questionId: "5",
    questionText: "What is the main topic of this descriptive text?",
    descriptionText:
      "“Mount Everest, the highest mountain on Earth, rises to an elevation of 8,848.86 meters (29,031.7 feet) above sea level. It is located in the Himalayas, straddling the border between Nepal and the Tibet Autonomous Region of China.”",
    options: [
      {
        id: "A",
        text: "Pyramid",
      },
      {
        id: "B",
        text: "Bali Island",
      },
      {
        id: "C",
        text: "Taj Mahal",
      },
      {
        id: "D",
        text: "Mount Everest",
      },
      {
        id: "E",
        text: "The Great Wall of China",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "D",
  },
  {
    questionId: "6",
    questionText: "Papua has a traditional house known as ...",
    descriptionText: "",
    options: [
      {
        id: "A",
        text: "Joglo",
      },
      {
        id: "B",
        text: "Gadang",
      },
      {
        id: "C",
        text: "Honai",
      },
      {
        id: "D",
        text: "Krong Bade",
      },
      {
        id: "E",
        text: "Kajang Lako",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "C",
  },
  {
    questionId: "7",
    questionText: "The size of a Honai house is ....",
    descriptionText: "",
    options: [
      {
        id: "A",
        text: "2.5 meters",
      },
      {
        id: "B",
        text: "2.4 meters",
      },
      {
        id: "C",
        text: "2.6 meters",
      },
      {
        id: "D",
        text: "2.7 meters",
      },
      {
        id: "E",
        text: "2.8 meters",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A",
  },
  {
    questionId: "8",
    questionText: "The following statement is true, except ….",
    descriptionText: "",
    options: [
      {
        id: "A",
        text: "Papua is home Honai typical inhabited by the Dani's.",
      },
      {
        id: "B",
        text: "Honai houses made of wood with a conical roof made of straw or reeds.",
      },
      {
        id: "C",
        text: "Honai house is divided into five types",
      },
      {
        id: "D",
        text: "Honai has a small door and no windows.",
      },
      {
        id: "E",
        text: "Honai has approximately 2.5 meters high.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "C",
  },
  {
    questionId: "9",
    questionText:
      "“Jerome Polin is a famous YouTuber from Indonesia. Jerome Polin was born in Surabaya on May 2, 1998. Jerome is nicknamed a mathematician because of his achievements in solving math problems in a short time. In addition, Jerome often shares his content with his friends “Waseda Boys” about life in Japan while he was studying at Waseda University. Jerome Polin has a kind, open, and sociable personality.”",
    descriptionText: "Who is described in the sentence above?",
    options: [
      {
        id: "A",
        text: "Maudy Ayunda",
      },
      {
        id: "B",
        text: "Jerome Polin",
      },
      {
        id: "C",
        text: "Raffi Ahmad",
      },
      {
        id: "D",
        text: "Laksamana Maeda",
      },
      {
        id: "E",
        text: "Yuki Kato",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    questionId: "10",
    questionText:
      "Based on the above description, it can be concluded that hamsters are animals that ...",
    descriptionText: "",
    options: [
      {
        id: "A",
        text: "Animals that are sensitive and prone to stress.",
      },
      {
        id: "B",
        text: "Animals that can fly.",
      },
      {
        id: "C",
        text: "Animals that are active during the day.",
      },
      {
        id: "D",
        text: "Meat-eating animals.",
      },
      {
        id: "E",
        text: "Animals that are fierce and like to bite.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A",
  },
  {
    questionId: "11",
    questionText: "",
    descriptionText: "The underlined word can be best replaced by …",
    options: [
      {
        id: "A",
        text: "Insufficient",
      },
      {
        id: "B",
        text: "Indiscipline",
      },
      {
        id: "C",
        text: "Ineffective",
      },
      {
        id: "D",
        text: "Inedible",
      },
      {
        id: "E",
        text: "Impossible",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "X",
  },
  {
    questionId: "12",
    questionText: "What is the purpose of the text?",
    descriptionText: "",
    options: [
      {
        id: "A",
        text: "to terrify the readers",
      },
      {
        id: "B",
        text: "to decribe the writer’s headmaster",
      },
      {
        id: "C",
        text: "to promote the writer’s headmaster career",
      },
      {
        id: "D",
        text: "to inform the readers about a terrifying school",
      },
      {
        id: "E",
        text: "to tells the story about a man",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    questionId: "13",
    questionText: "Where does Mr. Tucker usually wash his hands?",
    descriptionText: "",
    options: [
      {
        id: "A",
        text: "Corner of the room",
      },
      {
        id: "B",
        text: "In front of the room",
      },
      {
        id: "C",
        text: "Beside of the room",
      },
      {
        id: "D",
        text: "Behind of the room",
      },
      {
        id: "E",
        text: "Between of the room",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    questionId: "14",
    questionText: "",
    descriptionText: "The underlined word has similar meaning to…",
    options: [
      {
        id: "A",
        text: "Wash",
      },
      {
        id: "B",
        text: "Fold",
      },
      {
        id: "C",
        text: "Divide",
      },
      {
        id: "D",
        text: "Corner",
      },
      {
        id: "E",
        text: "Add",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "",
  },
  {
    questionId: "15",
    questionText:
      "How old is Lucy? And how is the age difference with the author?",
    descriptionText: "",
    options: [
      {
        id: "A",
        text: "ten",
      },
      {
        id: "B",
        text: "nine",
      },
      {
        id: "C",
        text: "four",
      },
      {
        id: "D",
        text: "three",
      },
      {
        id: "E",
        text: "eleven",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A",
  },
  {
    questionId: "16",
    questionText: "",
    descriptionText: "What opposite for the underlined word?",
    options: [
      {
        id: "A",
        text: "Big",
      },
      {
        id: "B",
        text: "Like",
      },
      {
        id: "C",
        text: "Care",
      },
      {
        id: "D",
        text: "Bad",
      },
      {
        id: "E",
        text: "Arrogant",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "B",
  },
  {
    questionId: "17",
    questionText: "When and by whom was Monas officially inaugurated?",
    descriptionText: "",
    options: [
      {
        id: "A",
        text: "July 12, 1975 by Soekarno",
      },
      {
        id: "B",
        text: "June 12, 1975 by Soekarno",
      },
      {
        id: "C",
        text: "July 12, 1957 by Soekarno",
      },
      {
        id: "D",
        text: "July, 12, 1975 by Soeharto",
      },
      {
        id: "E",
        text: "June, 12, 1975 by Soeharto",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A",
  },
  {
    questionId: "18",
    questionText: "The design Monas was created by...",
    descriptionText: "",
    options: [
      {
        id: "A",
        text: "Prabowo Subianto",
      },
      {
        id: "B",
        text: "Pangeran Diponegoro",
      },
      {
        id: "C",
        text: "Achmad Soebardjo",
      },
      {
        id: "D",
        text: "Freddy Subiantoro",
      },
      {
        id: "E",
        text: "Jenderal Soedirman",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "D",
  },
  {
    questionId: "19",
    questionText: `What does “Monas” stand for...`,
    descriptionText: "",
    options: [
      {
        id: "A",
        text: "Monumen Nanas",
      },
      {
        id: "B",
        text: "Monumen Nasional",
      },
      {
        id: "C",
        text: "Monumen Nasution",
      },
      {
        id: "D",
        text: "Monumen Nagasaki",
      },
      {
        id: "E",
        text: "Monumen Naritasan Shinshoji",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "B",
  },
  {
    questionId: "20",
    questionText: `Mr. Andi is a postman. Everyday he delivers many letters to many people. His wife, Mrs. Andi, is a Mathematics teacher. She teaches in SMA 1 Bandung. Mr. and Mrs. Andi has one son named Dani, and one daughter named Diana. Every weekend, Mr. Andi’s family always goes to hang out. Sometimes they go to a beach, a zoo, or a cafe.`,
    descriptionText: "Where is Mr. Ahmad work?",
    options: [
      {
        id: "A",
        text: "Hospital",
      },
      {
        id: "B",
        text: "Police office",
      },
      {
        id: "C",
        text: "Post office",
      },
      {
        id: "D",
        text: "School",
      },
      {
        id: "E",
        text: "Bank",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "C",
  },
];
